Guide to the Alfred E. Kahn papers, 1942-1994
Kahn, Alfred E. papers, 1942-1994
- Series IX. Speeches
  - Talk Univ. Minnesota Study Group Minneapolis 5/17/84, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Speech Natl Rest.Assn Chicago 5/20/84, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Speech Southeastern Asso. Reg. UtilComm. Nashville 5/21/84, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Speech Midwest Conf. Omaha 6/7/84, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Article PUF - June, 1984, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Speech Bell Core, Parsippany 6/22/84, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - EDP Cornell 6/25/84-6/26/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - EPRI Meeting Palo Alto 6/27/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Platter River Verified Statement 7/10/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Speech Niagara Mohawk Hamilton, NY 7/11/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Antitrust Seminar Aspen 7/12/84-7/14/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Food Exec Prog. 7/18/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Testimony Illinois Power - July, 1984, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - EDP Cornell Industrial Policy Speech 8/2/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Testimony Central Maine - Aug., 1984, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Talk Food Managament Program, CU 8/15/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Letter to Congress Airports 9/7/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Testimony Northwest Bell Nebraska - Sept., 1984, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Article Telematics Ames Revised - Sept., 1984, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Speech Bank Admin. Denver 9/14/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Talk Nera Denver 9/14/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Talk Purdue Dedication 9/15/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Speech NABE Atlanta 9/24/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Speech Amer. Auto Leasing 9/25/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - ICC Statement CSX - Oct., 1984, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Testimony Indiana Tel - Oct., 1984, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Speech INGAA - Boca, Raton 10/2/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Talk Nera London 10/9/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Speech NWBELL Des Moines, IA 10/16/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Speech Forum Springfield, MA 10/17/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Speech Ameritech Chicago 10/19/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Speech LaSalle Bank Chicago 10/24/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Speech Cornell Club Chicago Bureaucratese 10/24/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Speech Economic Issues in the Election 10/29/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Testimony NWBell Iowa Dereg 11/1/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Verified Statement OPPD - Nov., 1984, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Speech World Affairs Council Philadelphia 11/8/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Electric Power Conference NYPA New York 11/8/84-11/9/84, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Testimony SWBell OK - Apr., 1985, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Testimony Illinois Power Rebuttal - Apr., 1985, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Illinois Power Re-Cross, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Speech Institutional Investors Lake Como, Italy 4/22/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Speech Motana Power Butte 5/14/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Speech Shared Med Sys Hilton Head 5/15/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Speech NJ Bankers Hilton Head, SC 5/16/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - SUNY-Albany Honorary Degree 5/19/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Speech RPI/NYNEX Saratoga Springs 6/5/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Speech Data Resources NYC 6/11/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Speech Coll.Elec.Eng. Cornell 6/12/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Speech Niagara Mohawk Saratoga Springs 6/20/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Speech 4H Teen Congress 6/27/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Article Viewpoint MarshMac Magazine - July, 1985, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - EDP Program Bus. Sch. 7/1/85-7/3/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Testimony Southern Cal. Ed. - July, 1985, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Lecture Food Executives Cornell University 7/23/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Article WSJ on AEK 7/26/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Speech AM/FM IntT Vail 8/12/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Speech EDP Johnson Museum 8/15/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Frontier Issues in Telecommunications Regulation 8/20/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Telematics Response 8/21/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Rebuttal SWBellOK Oklahoma City 9/9/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Speech Tele. Seminar Hilton Head 9/10/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Book Review Bailey et al., Deregulating the Airlines - Sept., 1985, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Speech Bus and Coach Co. England 9/18/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Speech INTEREL/WSJ Brussels 9/18/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Speech Robert Morris Asso. Boston 9/23/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Article Airline Business - Sept., 1985, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Article IEEE Spectrum - Sept., 1985, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Speech N.E. Telephone Newport, RI 9/23/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Speech UConn Storrs 9/26/85, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - NERA Senior Staff Rye 9/26/85, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Speech Ebasco San Diego 10/2/85, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - CAPE Seminar Cornell 10/3/85, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Speech Ohio S&L League Cincinnati 10/8/85, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Speech SE Elec. Exch. Williamsburg 10/11/85, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Speech CMP Prout's Neck, Maine 10/11/85, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Talk FCC Conference Washington 10/18/85, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Colloquium NYLaw School 10/21/85, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Speech Quality Inns Atlanta 10/22/85, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Speech Bellcore New Orleans 10/23/85, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Talk Admin Law Group Washington 10/28/85, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - ERG Meeting Washington 10/29/85, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Testimony Illinois Bell Telephone 11/1/85, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Speech Kenyon College Gambier, Ohio 11/4/85, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Article Balance of Payments 11/12/85, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - London Trip - Nov., 1985, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Speech GEEC New York, NY 11/13/85, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Aviation Conference Singapore 11/21/85, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Testimony Arizona Public Service 12/2/85, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Speech Bell Canada Ottawa 12/16/85, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Testimony PP&L 1/6/86, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Testimony SCE XE - Jan., 1986, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Testimony Ahern Rebuttal SCE 1/10/86, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Speech Inst. Investors 1/10/86, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Speech NYSE Tarrytown 1/21/86, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - NBR Panel New York 1/29/86, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Net Taper Statement 1/30/86, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Speech Soc.Mgmt.Accnts. Toronto 2/4/86, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Panel Direct Dialogue Minneapolis 2/11/86, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - NERA Electric Util. Conf. Phoenix 2/12/86, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Speech Bank of America Chicago 2/19/86, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Speech GECC Los Angeles 2/20/86, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Speech Auto Service Ind. Chicago 2/24/86, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - Testimony House Judiciary Comm. Rodino 2/26/86, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - Conference Board Economic Forum NYC 2/28/86, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - Speech Oberlin College 3/7/86, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - Speech CU Business School Brussels 3/22/86, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - Speeches Airlines, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - CBS News 1/24/83, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - TakeTwo Cable News Appearance 2/4/83, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Talk to United Way Luncheon 2/8/83, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Moneyline, Cable News Appearance 2/14/83, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Lecture Hotel School 2/15/83, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Interview New Jersey Bell Magazine - Feb., 1983, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Memorial Service for Aunt Emily 3/20/83, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Talk Last Lecture Series Cornell West Campus 4/6/83, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Talk Reception for Cornell Alumni Greenwich, CT 5/22/83, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Honorary Degree Colgate University 5/29/83, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - CU Class of '53 Panel 6/11/83, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - ILR Cancelled 7/25/83, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Speech ABA-Atlanta Cancelled 8/1/83, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Talk Real Estate Conf. at CU Eco. Prospects 9/23/83, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Talk IBM Seminar 9/26/83, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Talk Cornell Club Rochester 10/26/83, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Talk Tompkins Co. Health Planners 2/23/84, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Tompkins Co. Sr. Citizens 3/8/84, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Talk to Medical Staff Tompkins Comm. Hospital 3/12/84, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Univ. of PA 4/11/84, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Lunch to Honor CAB Washington 4/16/84, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Talk Common Cause, Ithaca 4/26/84, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Ithaca Festival Ad 5/4/84, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Cable News Network Washington 5/7/84, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - BBC Interview - Aug., 1984, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Talk ILR Class on IndPol 9/26/84, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Transportation Research Award Boston 10/23/84, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Educational Film Center Interview Louis Barbash 10/31/84, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Nightline 1/2/85, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Firing Line NYC 1/7/85, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - Interview Mike Beilies 1/7/85, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - "Investing, Forcasting & A Grain of Salt" Campus Club 2/5/85, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 33)
  - Talk Johnson Wax Cornell 3/26/85, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 34)
  - Talk Entrepreneur's Day 4/12/85, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 35)
  - Talk Hilton Head Cornell Alumni 5/15/85, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 36)
  - Talk Spencer Christina Free Acad. 5/28/85, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 37)
  - Adam Smith's Money World PBS 6/9/85, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 38)
  - Interview CIN Cornell 10/17/85, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 39)
  - Belle Sherman School 12/10/85, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 40)
  - Talk Cornell Comm. on Ed. & Commty. 1/6/86, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 41)
  - Today Show Chicago 2/24/86, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 42)
  - Talk Food Execs. Cornell 7/22/86, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 43)
  - Talk BPA(Joe Thomas) 8/14/86, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 44)
  - Talk IBM/EDP ILR School 9/8/86, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 45)
  - Seminar Dick Ferris Cornell 11/5/86, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 46)
  - Energy Dialog Reddy Communications - Nov., 1986, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 47)
  - Speech Ithaca College 11/6/86, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 48)
  - Talk Cornell Alumni New York City 11/14/86, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 49)
  - Lecture Dick Aplin's Class Cornell 12/1/86, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 50)
  - Seminar Senior Citizens Ithaca 12/11/86, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 51)
  - Talk Ithaca Journal 12/16/86, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 52)
  - Talk New Eng. Tel Boston 2/13/87, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 53)
  - Talk Gioia Dinner 4/9/87, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 54)
  - Talk Brofenbrenner Tribute 4/26/87, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 55)
  - Talk Telecommunications Conf. Albany 4/29/87, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 56)
  - Cornell Alumni Class of '56 Reunion Weekend 6/13/87, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 57)
  - Lecture EDP/Bus.Sch. 6/29/87, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 58)
  - Eniaudi Comm. Dinner 11/6/87, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 59)
  - Talk Cornell Club Minneapolis 2/10/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 60)
  - Meeting with Peter Bradford NYC 2/18/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 61)
  - Chapter "In Defense of Dereg." - in McKelvey Book - Spring '88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 62)
  - Lecture Hotel School Cornell 3/8/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 63)
  - Meeting Telecommunications Nera, White Plains 3/9/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 64)
  - Speech Compen. Ins. New York City 4/6/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 65)
  - Speech GustavusAdolphus College, Minneapolis, MN 4/7/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 66)
  - Speech Cornell Club Milwaukee, WI 4/7/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 67)
  - Speech Nichols College Dudley, MA 4/19/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 68)
  - Lectures of BPA Cornell LindrSmileyClasses 4/25/88-4/27/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 69)
  - Talk Rotary Club of Minneapolis 5/4/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 70)
  - Speech Amer. Soc. of Bus. Editors&Writers St. Paul, MN 5/4/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 71)
  - Speech Economics Club of Sheboygan 5/5/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 72)
  - NBR Panel Pittsburgh, PA 5/11/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 73)
  - Firing Line 6/9/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 74)
  - Talk to Summer College Students at Cornell 7/14/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 75)
  - Carter Luncheon Atlanta, GA 7/18/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 76)
  - Summer Session Lecture Cornell Bailey Hall 7/20/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 77)
  - Dept. of Trans. Cambridge, MA 7/26/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 78)
  - Speech Cornell Prog. in Prof. Edu. 8/9/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 79)
  - Woodside Travel New York City 9/26/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 80)
  - Speech ILR School Cornell Univ. 9/29/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 81)
  - Speech Nice, France 10/13/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 82)
  - Speech Aero Club Washington, D.C. 10/25/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 83)
  - Speech U. of N. Carolina Raleigh, NC 10/25/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 84)
  - CAU Weekend Skytop, PA 10/28/88-10/30/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 85)
  - Speech Rotary Club, Ithaca 11/23/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 86)
  - Lectures 2 Dick Aplin's Ag Ec at Cornell 11/28/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 87)
  - Talk Cornell Economics Society 12/7/88, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 88)
  - Speech Nat'l Grocers Las Vegas, NV 2/1/89, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 89)
  - Speech Irving Leasing LA Quinta, CA 2/7/89, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 90)
  - Speech GE Capital San Juan, Puerto Rico 3/11/89, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 91)
  - Reception/Bob Nathan Washington, DC 3/30/89, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 92)
  - Speech Gordon Center, Brandeis Univ. 3/31/89, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 93)
  - Talk Neuborne Seminar 4/20/89, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 94)
  - ERG, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 95)
  - Teach Cornell Bob Smiley's Class 4/26/89-4/27/89, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 96)
  - Speech Atlas Van Lines Chicago, IL 5/5/89, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 97)
  - Food Executive Program Dr. Fred Kahn 7/24/89, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 98)
  - Talk Manufac. Techonology Cornell 9/18/89, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 99)
  - Public Power Seminar 9/21/89, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 100)
  - Talk United Way Ithaca 9/29/89, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 101)
  - Talk: Mississippi College 11/7/89, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 102)
  - NERA Sr. Staffmeeting Greenwhich, CT 10/16/89-10/18/89, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 103)
  - Eastern Europe Speeches, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 104)
  - Talk Wall St. Group New York 2/8/90, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 105)
  - Talk S. Arkansas U. 4/18/90, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 106)
  - Talk Cancun ASTA 4/19/90-4/21/90, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 107)
  - Talk Oklahoma City 4/24/90, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 108)
  - Talk Cornell Engineering Conference 4/27/90, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 109)
  - IBM International Personal Executive Seminar 9/27/90, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 110)
  - Talk NY Power Auth. Memphis, Tenn. 10/22/90, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 111)
  - CAD Breakfast Talk - Jan., 1991, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 112)
  - Talks New York/NJ VTS Travel 3/20/91-3/21/91, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 113)
  - Talks/Classes Roanoke College 3/25/91-3/28/91, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 114)
  - Co-op Extension Teleconference 5/18/91, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 115)
  - Speech Digital Equip. Pebble Beach 6/12/91, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 116)
  - Panel Nightly Business New York City 6/13/91, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 117)
  - Speech Chicago, IL National Business Travel 7/24/91, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 118)
  - Talk Cornell Energy Seminar 10/24/91, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 119)
  - Meeting Profs. Neely/Askinson, AT&T 4/25/91, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 120)
  - Book Review Patent System - Jan., 1992, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 121)
  - Meeting/Speech Ottawa, Ontario 9/16/92, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 122)
  - EEA Panel Washington, DC 3/20/93, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 123)
  - Edison Electric Mtg Washington, DC 3/31/93, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 124)
  - American Bar Assoc. Washington, DC 3/31/93, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 125)
  - Talk Cornell Engr. 10/28/93, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 126)
  - Speech First Albany San Juan, P.R. 1/26/94, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 127)
  - NERA Antitrust Seminar Santa fe, NM 7/7/94-7/9/94, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 128)
  - Speech American Actuarial Asso. Boston 11/12/84, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 129)
  - Economic Stablization Cmte-House Cmte on Banking, etc 3/19/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Testimony Before Senate Finance Subcom. on Finance 3/19/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Issues & Answers Sunday 3/23/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Democratic House & Senate Council 3/26/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Testimony to House Cmte on Appropriations 3/31/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Plain English Conference Four Seasons Hotel DC 4/2/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - "Meet the Regulators" - American Enterprise Institute 4/3/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Arizona Center for Law in the Public Interest Phoenix 4/7/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Arizona State Legislature Phoenix 4/8/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Articles, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - American Society of Newspaper Editors Wash Hilton 4/9/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Industry Meetings Spring 1980, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Speech to Washington Journalism Center Watergate 4/14/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - State Attorneys General Mayflower Hotel 4/15/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Dallas Texas Trip - Press & Businessman 4/18/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Testimony to Senate Cmte on Banking, Housing 4/21/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Talk to the Conference Board NYC 4/22/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Testimony to Senate Appropriations Subcmte 4/23/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Testimony to Subcmte on Economic Stablization - House Banking 4/30/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Testimony to House Banking Cmte Subcmte on Eco. Stablization 5/6/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Int'l Corporate Leadership Seminar Wye-Aspen Institute 5/7/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Article on Myron Watkins, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Ripon Commencement Speech 5/18/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - National Journal Health Policy Conference Speech 6/17/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - American Stock Exchange Symposium Dept. of State 6/23/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures NYC 7/10/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Conference on Innovative Regulatory Techniques 7/22/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Birmingham/Anniston, Alabama 9/3/80-9/4/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Common Cause 9/5/80, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Speech NARUC Los Angeles 11/26/84, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Speech Nat'l Conf State Legis New Orleans 11/29/84, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Speech MIT Econ Forum Cambridge 12/6/84, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Speech Chamber of Comm. Hartford 12/6/84, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Speech Kodak Mgmt. Club Rochester 12/11/84, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Panel AEA III Dallas 12/28/84, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Speech AEA III Dallas 12/28/84, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Rebuttal Platte River 12/84, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Speech Insurance Inf. Inst. New York 1/17/85, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - NERA Conf. on Telecomm. Wigman 1/24/85-1/26/85, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Article Living Publications 2/85, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Testimony CMP Rebuttal 2/85, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Testimony CMP Re-Cross 2/85, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Speech Airline Conference Phoenix 2/7/85, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Speech Tel. Competition Salt Lake City 2/18/85, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - Verified Statement Iowa Public Service 2/27/85, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - Speech Conference Board 3/7/85, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - Comments DOT (Pevsner) 3/12/85, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 18)
  - Speech Brookings Inst. 3/14/85, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 19)
  - Speech Planmetrics 3/18/85, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - Testimony CRS 3/19/85, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - Speech Inside Gas Mkts Washington 3/25/85, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 22)
  - Talk Harvard Bus. Sch. 3/27/85, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - Article Federal News & J 1/86, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 24)
  - New York Air, 1982 (Box 105, Folder 25)
  - Speech NY Air Dedication 12/11/80, 1980 (Box 105, Folder 26)
  - Nightly Business Report, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 27)
  - Testimony to Aviation Subcommittee House Public Works 3/6/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Pan Am Int'l Advisory Board, Semi-Annual Mtg., Washington 4/3/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Transportation Council of Associated Industries 4/19/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Club - Lecture Washington, D.C. 5/8/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Sixth Annual Telecommunications Policy Research Conf., Airlie, VA 5/10-13/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Speech at the Int'l Aviation Club 5/16/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - American Association of Airport Executives-Annual Conference Cincinnati, Ohio 5/21-24/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Federal Bar Association Tom C. Clark Award 5/31/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Aifreignt Forwarders Association Luncheon Speech 6/2/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - "Applying Economics to an Imprefect World," University of Va. Conference, Charlottesvill, Va. 6/5/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Alumni Weekend 6/9/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Testimony Before Senate Subcomm. On S. 3064-Noise Bill 6/14/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - TAA Board of Directors Mtg. Washington, D.C. 6/14/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Lou Harris & Associates - Seminar Washington, D.C. 6/29/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - MacNeil Lehrer Show 7/5/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - DOT Legal Speakers' Program 7/19/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Testimony Before Anti-Trust Commission 7/26/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - American Bar Association (ABA) "A Paean to Legal Creativity" NYC 8/8/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - Talk to ALJ's Washington 8/18/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Testimony on S. 3363 International Air Trans Comp Act 78 8/23/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - Speech by Kahn at the Annual Meeting of the American Economic Assn., Chicago 8/26/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Ely Lecture Chicago 8/29/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - White House Meetings on Deregulation Bill 9/11/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 23)
  - Talk at American Stock Exchange New York 9/18/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 24)
  - Nat'l Assn. of Business Economists, New Orleans 9/22/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 25)
  - NASAO Speech Indianapolis 9/27/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 26)
  - Financial Times Conference London, England 10/2-4/78, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 27)
  - Speakers Bureau, 1980 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Southern Bell, 1983 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Southern California Edison Company, 1985 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Southern California Edison - Westinghouse, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - New York State Advisory Panel on Telecommunications, 1983 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - New York State Cable TV Study, 1980 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Nine Miles 2, 1982 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Owens - Illinois, 1981 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - PA Bell, 1982 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Paribas - Hold, 1985 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Memo to President Carter 12/12/80, 1980 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Route 96 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Rochester Telephone Co., 1985 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Schlesinger, Arthur Jr., 1979 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Taps Cross-Examination, 1984 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Senator Tsongas, 1981 (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Villa Banfi, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Good Morning America 9/12/80, 1980 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Boston & The Advocates Taping 9/23/80, 1980 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - American Enterprise Institute 9/26/80, 1980 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - San Jose & San Francisco 9/27-28/80, 1980 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Small - Hydro Meeting 10/3/80, 1980 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Norfolk, Virginia 10/6/80, 1980 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Rochester/Ithaca 10/15/80, 1980 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Johns Hopkins University 10/29/80, 1980 (Box 120, Folder 8)